Curriculum Vitae 2019 Hanh Pham

About

22 year-old, German-born student, studying <u>Visual</u> <u>Communication Design in Mannheim</u>.

I'm interested in digital, interactive and human-centered design. At the same time (or maybe because of that) I think a lot about effective and fulfilling team work. All this drives me to try and work in international and interdisciplinary settings, as getting to know as many different people as possible is key for the kind of design I strive to create.

Basic information

Pham, Phuc Hanh
Born 23rd April 1996
hanhpham@protonmail.com
Inquire via e-mail for more
personal information

Education

09 2015—now Enrolled at the Faculty of Design, Visual Communication Design

University of Applied Sciences Mannheim, Germany

02 2018 — 06 2018 Theoretical semester abroad

Hongik University, Seoul, South Korea

06 2014 Graduated High School with grade 1.6

Hebelgymnasium Schwetzingen, Germany

Work Experiences

09 2018-01 2019 Mentor and moderator for an interdisciplinary, university wide

team project class kompass

University of Applied Sciences Mannheim, Germany

02 2017—now PR office student associate

University of Applied Sciences Mannheim, Germany

02 2017-04 2017 Student associate of MAD Lab, interactive media lab at the Faculty

of Design

University of Applied Sciences Mannheim, Germany

Volunteer work

09 2017–03 2018 Member of various student councils and panels

University of Applied Sciences Mannheim, Germany

06 2016—12 2016 Editorial Designer at komma magazine

01 2015—now Voluntary German Teacher for refugees

Refugee Camp Schwetzingen, Germany

Skills

+++ Adobe Cloud, Processing, Arduino, Cinema 4D

++++ HTML, CSS

+++++ German (native), English

++ Korean, Vietnamese

+++++ Presentations, Visualising and sketching

+++++ Team moderation and organisation

Coming soon Spanish, Chinese, JavaScript

Letter of Recommendation

Prof. Kai Beiderwellen

"[...] She develops outstanding creative approaches, that she implements with a high design competence and certainty. In cooperation with students from our department of informatics she could prove her teamworking skills.

These skills and the great originality of her work, made us regard her as one of the most talented and outstanding students in her year. [...]"